<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: mobile | ANML Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://agileanimal.github.com/blog/categories/mobile/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://agileanimal.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2012-01-18T00:30:14-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://agileanimal.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Mark Madsen]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Roam Mobility']]></title>
    <link href="http://agileanimal.github.com/blog/2012/01/17/blawgin/"/>
    <updated>2012-01-17T17:18:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://agileanimal.github.com/blog/2012/01/17/blawgin</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2>Finally, a great way to <a href="http://www.roammobility.com/">Roam</a>.</h2>

<p>This really is the best idea I've heard in a long time.</p>

<p><a href="http://www.roammobility.com/">Roam Mobility</a> is an operator that provides Canadians with a pay-as-you-go US phone number. They are really reasonably priced and you only need to use the service once a year to maintain your US number.</p>

<p>I was travelling in the US recently and Having this service would have saved me about $50 -- that is just one trip. If you are a frequent traveller you should look into both their data and voice services.</p>

<p>I've read some comments in forums where people are questioning the value provided by the service and instead suggest that you're better off dealing directly with US Carriers. I have used pay-as-you-go services from AT&amp;T and T-Mobile -- I think Roam is providing a much simpler and more cost effective way in the long run.  On my last trip I even tried to get Verizon to Activate a "Verizon Jetpack" for me -- they couldn't do it because their 4G network is only available on contract.</p>

<p>Just a word to the wise, their partner is T-Mobile -- this means you need a phone with AWS to get 3G/3.5G/3.667G/3.9999G/4.01G/etc. Your iPhone will roam on their Edge network but it will be slow. You should pick up a Nexus S with AWS (they go for about $350 these days but DO NOT have Rogers/Bell/Telus 3G) or a Galaxy Nexus (double the price at around $700 but works with everyone's 3G) if you are looking for a phone to use.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
